https://www.environmentcontrol.com/privacy-policy.php

Environment Control
Services
About
About Us
Why Choose Environment Control?
News
Our Locations
About
About Us
Why Choose Environment Control?
Environment Control Respects Your Privacy
Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Environment Control.
External Sites
Environment Control is not responsible for the content of external Internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.
Cookies
A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Environment Control to recognize you each time you visit this site (customization, etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Environment Control does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by third-party content providers such as newsfeeds.
Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet
While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Environment Control and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition, other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Environment Control have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.
Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.
Environment Control has made consistency the trademark of our commercial cleaning services.
Our customized programs are designed to increase your productivity, save you money, and give you peace of mind in regards to the cleanliness of your building.
Site Map
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
© 2020 Environment Control. All rights reserved. Site by Caliber Media Group
Environment Control has made consistent quality the trademark of our commercial cleaning services. Our customized cleaning programs are designed to increase your productivity, save you money, and give you peace of mind in the cleanliness of your facility.
Site Map
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
View Desktop Version
© 2020 Environment Control.All rights reserved.Site by Caliber Media Group
